itrust.in 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy - iTrust

We (Indian Dream Financial Advisors Pvt. Ltd using brand name - “iTrust”) receive personal information through this website. You may, for example, be asked for personal information if you want to take advantage of specific services that we offer, such as providing response to your queries.

Where you provide personal information, we will only use it to deliver the services you have requested. 

The iTrust site does not automatically capture or store personal information, other than logging your IP address and session information such as length of your visit and the type of browser used. This is recognised by the web server. These data are only used for system administration and to provide user statistics, which we use to evaluate how the site is being used and how we can improve usability.

We use cookies to make sure your session on this website is secure. We also use embedded pixels, with cookies. These help us track how many people are using our site. These collect data about the paths that users take when navigating our website. We use this information to evaluate site content, navigability and composition, as well as page response rates (how quickly pages download). With both cookies and embedded pixel technology, the information we collect is anonymous and does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. We cannot personally identify you. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to our homepage and other places we deem appropriate. After we have posted changes, if you use the iTrust website or any microsite within it you will be bound by the terms of change to our new privacy policy.

#### What else you should know about privacy

Remember to close your browser when you have finished your user session. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or an Internet cafe. As an individual, you are responsible for the security of, and access to, your own computer.

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information over the Internet that this information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information in publicly accessible online forums, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your usernames and passwords and any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are using the Internet.

#### Our Websites may contain links to other websites, and you should be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices on other websites.
